freebielist.com 2002-08-11

# FreebieList.com: Privacy Policy

_ Introduction to personal information _   
Personal information (information that you can personally be identified from) is readily misused over the Internet. The vast majority of Web sites will at some point ask you to provide your e-mail address and/or other personal information. This privacy statement, produced independently by FreebieList.com ([http://www.freebielist.com](http://www.freebielist.com/)) outlines the privacy practices of this Web site and aims to answer common questions on the "privacy" topic.

This site contains links to other sites. Note that FreebieList.com is not responsible for the privacy practices, content or security of data stored on such Web sites. FreebieList.com allows other sites to link to the URL [http://www.freebielist.com](http://www.freebielist.com/) as they wish, provided an approved image or text link is used. Examples of approved images can be found [here](http://www.freebielist.com/linkto.htm). We reserve the right to request a link removal from any Web site as needed. You may not create your own images and link to us.

Although the amount of personal details we collect is minimal, FreebieList.com does gather a considerable amount of information regarding your Internet Service Provider "ISP", country of origin/location, operating system, browser version, IP (Internet Protocol) address and time of visit. This information is logged by two different sources - our server logs and general purpose visitor tracker, maintained by WebTrends Live ([http://www.webtrendslive.com](http://www.webtrendslive.com/)). Visitors who access FreebieList.com via Web browsing software cannot be personally identified from the information we automatically collect, so accordingly, we only use this data for  demographic purposes and never distribute it to third parties. The sections below explain how we use the information collected.

_How we use the information provided_

**Our Newsletter - Your e-mail address is completely safe!**  
FreebieList.com operates a free, "opt-in" style mailing list to inform its members of the latest freebies, free services and webmaster tools. Membership of this newsletter is voluntary and you are asked to provide your e-mail address, surname and last name, gender, date of birth, post code and country. The mailing list provider that FreebieList.com uses, Topica ([http://www.topica.com](http://www.topica.com/)) holds all of this information and has its own privacy practices in place to avoid the loss or mishandling of your information. At this point, we feel we ought to mention that FreebieList.com has access to your e-mail addresses for unsubscription or modification purposes, but cannot view your "Topica" password or gain access to any area of your Topica account. FreebieList.com respects your privacy, and therefore will never disclose your e-mail address to any third parties.

**Internet Cookies - Your privacy is respected by all parties!**  
We use an outside advertisement company to display adverts on our Web site. These adverts may contain cookies and while we don't use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner adverts are collected by our advertisements company, and we do not have access to this information. For further information on TribalFusion's privacy policy visit [http://www.tribalfusion.com](http://www.tribalfusion.com/). If you require further information on Internet "cookies", please refer to: <http://privacy.net/cookies/>. 

**Web Traffic Analysers - Only FreebieList.com has access!**  
FreebieList.com uses advanced trackers and server logs to monitor the amount of data, visitors, responses and referrals that our host computer generates. These trackers also log IP addresses and various other information such as your time of visit, browser version, operating system and country of origin. We recognise your right to privacy and will never sell this information to any third parties. All server logs are protected by passwords, firewalls and other software/hardware security features.

**Security Measures - We keep all your details secure and safe!  
**Here at FreebieList.com, we have numerous security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We make every effort to ensure that any information collected is kept secure. Even so, we strongly recommended you never send personal information via electronic mail or other similar means. If you decide to do so, FreebieList.com will not be held responsible for information being intercepted by any third party. While we strive to keep the information that you supply directly or indirectly secure, please be aware that the Internet and WWW is not a fully secure medium.

_Changes to this policy  
_FreebieList.com will make changes to this privacy policy as new (or additional) procedures are implemented that concern the handling of your information. If you as a user are concerned with the privacy practices of this Web site, you may view this page as often as you wish however, accept that updates and/or corrections may be undertaken without any notification to you.

_Contacting FreebieList.com_  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with FreebieList.com, please [contact us](http://www.freebielist.com/contact.htm) and we'll be more than happy to help you out!
